Coordonnées

www.linkedin.com/in/thang-tran-79b959147 (LinkedIn)

Principales compétences

Java Web Development Spring Framework

Thang Tran

Java Software Engineer

District de Hoan Kiem

Résumé

I have work as a java web developer for more than a year until 2019/8.

I have experience in many projects, I start working when i finished University. My first company is a Korean IT company so i can communicate quite well by English.

Expérience

TechAsians JSC Java Software Engineer mai 2020 - juillet 2021 (1 an 3 mois) Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

MMGVN

Web Developer septembre 2018 - mai 2020 (1 an 9 mois) Hanoi, Vietnam

VNPT IT

Java Web Developer janvier 2017 - juin 2017 (6 mois) hanoi

Formation

Hanoi Open Unversity

Bachelor's degree, Information Technology · (2014 - 2018)

Activité

10/29/2021, Vu par Nga Lê (Lenka)